What the hell were you thinking, Mr. Westcott?
Please do enlighten us.
Sorry, I'm not quite sure what you're asking, Murdoch.
Now's not the time to play dumb.
I'm obviously referring to your many recent activities in Japan.
Interfering with the self-defense force,
utilizing wizards for your own agenda,
and worse, transforming the city into a war zone.
The Japanese government is all over us thanks to you.
How do you plan to rectify this mess?
Look, what does it matter?
We obviously achieved enough to make it worthwhile.
Don't forget, we succeeded with Princess's inversion.
Do you really not understand what I'm saying?
It's ludicrous.
What do spirits have to do with saving D.E.M.?
The company can't afford to take a backseat to your selfish little obsessions.
Everyone, I think the time has come.
I move that managing director Westcott be relieved of his position.
Are you willing to comply with this, sir?
Of course.
Removing me is well within your given rights as the board of directors.
Well then, Chairman Russell, I say we proceed with a vote right now.
All right.
All those in favor of Westcott's dismissal.
Zero hands.
His removal is hereby rejected.
What?
What are you talking about, Chairman?
All these people agree with me.
You'll find realizers ready at the infirmary.
If you get there fast, you should be back to normal in a few days.
And once I'm finished addressing my selfish little obsession,
I shall hand over the company.
Soon.
Don't worry.
At least compared to how long we've already been waiting, anyway.
A written challenge.
And with it, 12 photographs.
For one question,
can you find me?
Don't worry.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's true.
She seems different from Kurumi.
I have a feeling Natsumi may not be satisfied playing around and keeping it light.
The fact is, someone here may already be gone for eternity.
No, I don't think Natsumi is like that.
If I can just guess who she's impersonating, I know they'll come home in one piece.
Sounds like you're putting a lot of faith in this witch.
Think about it.
Could you open up your heart to someone if you didn't think they trusted you?
As if you know women at all.
Though, I will admit that was accurate.
Mm-hmm.
Whatever the case, we need to hurry.
Sorry, Coterie.
I'm afraid you'll have to stay away from command.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I could just as easily be Natsumi as anyone else could.
And you, Shin, you have an awful lot of work ahead of you.
Okay, what should I do?
For the time being, I'd start by deciding the order you'll be dating them in.
To see through Natsumi's disguise, be careful not to overlook even the smallest differences from the norm.
You'll date them one by one in search of anything that seems off.
Feels wrong somehow to go out on dates while I'm doubting everyone.
Oh, good morning, Shido!
I'm sorry, were you waiting long?
Not at all. You're right on time.
This has to be Toka. I mean, look at her.
Is anything wrong, Shido?
You seem a lot more quiet than usual.
You think? No, I'm super great, really!
Try to relax, Shin.
Remember, she's good at this.
You won't see through her disguise easily.
Let's try to shake her up a bit.
Hey, Toka.
Would you remind me when we went out last?
I can't remember.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Have you forgotten that we went shopping just a few days ago?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
She got it.
So, what's next?
But I don't mind going out again so soon, just so you know.
It's one of the things that makes me the happiest.
Toka.
I'm totally on to you.
Huh?
You play Toka well, right, Natsumi?
Wait, are you not?
Shido?
Who the heck is this Natsumi?
Don't try to pretend like you didn't just blurt out another girl's name, Shido!
You better tell me where this other girl is right now!
No, you misunderstood.
That's a kind of a greeting.
It started in an island down south, and now it's caught on in Japan, too.
Natsumi!
See?
Is that true?
Wow, what an incredible lie.
It's so bad, it almost has to be real.
Oh, okay.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
So, when they use Natsumi as a greeting, what does it mean?
Uh, well, I'm pretty sure it means I love you.
Or something close.
I see.
Oh, also, what did you mean when you said I play Toka well?
Wow, Toka, check it out!
That restaurant is totally doing a lunch buffet!
We have to get in there and take advantage!
You want to get lunch?
Sure, I mean, I could eat.
All right, let's do it then.
Wait a minute, what is this reaction?
Normally, one mention of food would instantly cheer her up.
So far, we've had no detection of Natsumi.
How has it felt on your end?
I'm thinking it's gotta be the real Toka.
But we're here to eat lunch and she seems so...
Problem?
What, is something the matter, Shido?
Oh, no.
No way! Toka only filled half her plate?
Strange. I wonder if she's sick.
That's absurd!
She's always a bottomless pit, no matter what!
Hey, were you waiting for me?
Thanks, let's eat up.
Right. Yeah, we should.
Is it true?
Is Toka really not Suni?
Thanks for the lunch.
You're done?
What's wrong, Toka?
That couldn't have been enough food for you.
No, it's okay.
I...
I saw something on TV.
You have to be careful.
Girls who regularly eat a lot more than guys
can sometimes be a real turn-off.
See, the thing is,
I didn't want you to be turned off by me,
so I thought I would eat less.
Actually,
I really prefer girls who are happy
to scarf down lots of food.
Do you mean it?
Yeah, it's definitely Toka.
Fine.
But we still can't dismiss her just yet.
Stay with Toka and let her finish eating.
But make sure to get back home
by at least 3 o'clock.
Your next date will come over
and meet you there.
Yep!
Hang on, I'm coming!
Boo!
Ah!
Might want to be more careful, Shido.
Uh, right, thanks.
I just wasn't expecting to see you.
Then I guess today's your lucky day!
Oh, man.
Sorry about that, Yoshino.
Yoshinan kind of surprised me.
Ah, trick-or-treat.
If you don't give me any candy,
I think I have to prank you.
Shido, this is so...
I have to say,
I never thought you'd come here trick-or-treating.
Afraid we're all out of candy.
I hope the hotcakes will do.
This is a first for me.
I've never had them.
I see.
Well, I hope you enjoy.
You had the same reaction
the first time you came here, remember?
Let me see.
Remind me what it was you ate that day.
Oh, what was it?
That's right.
You made Oyakodan for me.
Ah, yes.
That was it.
Oh, what are you talking about, Shido?
That doesn't ring a bell to me.
You don't remember?
No.
I wonder, though.
Do you think it could have been
during that time
when I stayed over at Origami's?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot that ever happened.
I actually had to invade Origami's place
to get you back, didn't I?
Oh, sure.
Huh?
Come on, just do it.
What would you think
about sharing this with me?
No, that's okay.
I mean, I made those especially for you.
Oh, all right, fine.
We can share.
Give me a bite.
Say, ah.
Ah.
Isn't that yummy?
Mm-hmm.
It really is.
Shido, you've got a little syrup.
Huh?
Where is it?
Whoa!
Hot cakes are, like,
halfway between a food and a candy, actually.
So that's why, why I just...
It was just a prank, okay?
Whoa, whoa!
You go, girl!
Hey, Reina,
I think that was the real Yoshino,
don't you?
Well, who knows, really.
So, who's up next on the agenda?
Right.
Hirito,
Tonomachi.
Toka,
Yoshino,
and Tonomachi.
We're three dates down
with no real leads
on what we're looking for.
None of their behavior
seemed any different
than usual to any of us.
I'd prefer not to call
that whole thing
with Tonomachi a date,
if that's okay.
Shin,
think you can handle one more?
Yuzuru is already waiting for you
at the designated location.
Absolutely.
Sorry, Yuzuru.
Offended.
Some nerve inviting me here
and arriving late.
What do you have to say?
So sorry.
I was running a bit behind.
Pardoned.
It's all right.
You'll find I have a big heart,
so we will just call
those five minutes
an anomaly.
Are you unhappy
that I'm the only one here?
No, that's not it at all.
I was just thinking
what a rare occasion this is.
Negative.
Please don't feel as if
you need to make
some kind of excuse.
Kaguya and I
are of one heart and mind.
In fact, what you said
it only serves to validate
how closely she and I
are bound together.
Question.
Is there anything wrong
that I should know about?
You've never called me out
this late.
Oh, nothing.
I just thought it might be nice
to talk with you alone
once in a while.
Bad idea?
Negative.
It's not bad at all.
But if that's the case...
Y-Yusuru?
Selfishness.
Just for tonight,
Shido is mine and mine alone.
And it's nice.
Suggestion.
Shido,
shall we take a walk together?
Whoa.
Admiration.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, it sure is.
Advice.
Whenever a girl says
that something is beautiful,
it's common knowledge
the only appropriate response
from a guy is
but you are more beautiful.
Is that really how it is?
Affirmative.
That is just how it is.
Well,
you are more beautiful.
Happiness.
Do you mean it, though?
Uh,
huh?
Confrontation.
Shido?
Yeah?
What is it?
Question.
Answer, please.
When it comes to Kaguya and me,
which of us do you like more?
I can't answer that
off the top of my head.
You're both too precious.
Disdain.
Good grief, Shido.
You picked the most pathetic
and lazy answer
that there ever was.
What did you expect?
You popped that question
out of nowhere.
Concession.
Okay, then.
If I gave you enough time,
do you think you would be able
to answer me?
Uh,
uh,
if I do that,
which answer
are you hoping to hear?
Response.
If you end up choosing
Kaguya,
then I'll agree
and you're a good person.
I'd be disappointed in you
if you chose me.
Yeah,
I did not expect that.
Addition.
If you were to choose me instead,
I'd be happy.
Well,
which is it in the end?
Sigh.
It's just like I said.
I'd be fine with your choosing
either one of us.
However,
your answer was gutless.
That was a bummer,
Shido.
You're a big chicken.
Although,
petition.
One thing.
Promise me this.
If Kaguya ever comes to you
and asks you to answer
the same question
that I did,
when the time comes,
I want you to tell her
that she's the one you choose.
Prediction.
Kaguya will get mad at you.
She'll want to know
why you didn't pick me.
But,
deep inside,
she'll be so happy
that it hurts.
Yusuru.
Confidence.
Kaguya may behave strangely,
but she really does
love you very much.
And this is me saying it,
so it must be true.
The things that Kaguya hates,
I hate as well.
And likewise,
the things that I love,
Kaguya loves just as much.
Careless.
I said more than I meant to.
Before I blurt out anything else,
I should just go.
Come on,
please stay.
Petition.
What I've said to you
is no lie.
Kaguya really is
extremely taken by you.
So please,
do me a favor.
Be good to her for me.
Wait,
Yusuru!
Come back!
And?
You just came right home
after that?
After a date?
You made a girl walk home
at night in the dark
all by herself?
I gotta say,
you are not impressing me
with these choices.
Sorry.
It all happened so fast.
There's not much else
that could have been done.
From start to finish,
Shin has worked
very hard today.
Look,
I'm well aware of that.
Going on four dates
in a single day
wouldn't necessarily
be an easy task
for anybody.
So,
Shido.
Toka,
Yoshino,
Tonomachi,
and Yuzuru.
Any thoughts on
whether or not
Natsumi might have
been impersonating
one of them?
I just can't say
for sure.
I want so much
to believe
everyone was real.
Great.
Don't tell me
you ever thought
this would be easy.
No suspicious readings
on Fraxinus,
so I agree with Shin
if that helps.
Until we get more data
from the next round of dates,
it's anyone's guess.
Ugh,
fine.
Then go and get
some rest,
Shido.
You'll be no help
to us if you're
sleep-deprived.
Screw up your dates
tomorrow and it'll be
a problem for more
than just you.
Thanks for that.
Reyna,
tomorrow starts at
ten,
is that right?
Yes.
And the first of the day
is Coterie.
Now I see.
That's why.
No,
you are so wrong.
Just as the commander
I feel...
Why are you all
spaced out?
Go to bed already!
We can.
Hello,
I'm back home.
Yuzuru?
Hey,
what was your
urgent business?
Trivial.
Just something
I needed to take care of.
It is time,
Hanyel.
I'll pick the first one.
Will you even be able
to guess who I am
before every last one
is taken?
What's the deal?
It's so early
in the morning.
Shiro!
Rakuya?
She's gone.
When I woke up,
Yuzuru was gone!
How's Kaguya?
Better than she was
this morning.
To be safe,
I'm having
Touka and Yoshino
stay with her.
I think she'll be okay.
Yuzuru had to be taken
to Ratatasker HQ
for an urgent exam.
Or so we'll say.
Though,
if Kaguya is
Natsumi disguised,
then it's a
completely pointless lie.
Reina,
your thoughts?
Who could take
Yuzuru?
Are we sure
it was Natsumi?
Yes.
Look at this.
Is that...
Video from
a security camera.
The 12 people
Natsumi identified
with those photos
are being watched
around the clock.
This is footage
from last night.
I don't see anything
out of the ordinary here.
Keep watching.
Hey, that's
Natsumi's...
Yuzuru!
As you can see,
Yuzuru has been abducted
by Natsumi's angel.
Also,
it's likely that
whoever she's impersonating
has been erased
this way too.
Natsumi...
I don't understand.
Why do this?
Deciphering her intentions
can wait.
Right now,
we have to focus.
Keep people safe.
I do believe
in Natsumi.
I think this is just
a game to her.
Which is why
I'm going to put
an end to all this
before anyone else
disappears.
I agree,
Shido.
Let's not spare
any effort.
So I guess
it's about time
we begin our date.
How can I know
that in the days
that followed,
I would learn
just how powerless
I truly was?
You and the last
約束
をしよう
傷だらけのままで
しまい込んでた
心
ときみは
そっと
拾い上げた
繰り返す
旅に
どうしようもなく
紡いだとき
ぎゅっと
抱きしめてくれた
ずっと
ここで
きみと
ふたりで
夜空
流れる
星を
見続けたい
きみと
最後の
約束
をしよう
世界から
私だけ
消えてしまっても
気づかれなくていい
このままで
いたい
刻まれた
この気持ち
いつまでも
永遠に
どじ
それ крепい
ご視聴ありがとうございました
な
気づくり